<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Configuration on Suntimes</title>
    <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Configuration on Suntimes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/welcome/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/welcome/index.html</guid>
      <description>Suntimes will display a welcome screen to assist with initial configuration.
Appearance User Interface Location Time Zone Alarms Tip The welcome screen is automatically displayed the first time the app is launched. It can be revisited later from Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; General -&amp;gt; Welcome.
Appearance Suntimes supports light and dark themes, and can switch between them to match the system. It also includes high contrast versions of these themes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Select a Place</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/selectplace/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/selectplace/index.html</guid>
      <description>Suntimes requires location data to configure dialogs, alarms, and widgets.
It is recommended to configure the app to some user-defined location (such as a local park, intersection, or city center). Suntimes can also periodically query and update using the current location.
User-Defined Location Current (last known) User-Defined Location Suntimes is configured to a user-defined location by default. The use of location permissions is optional.
Configure the location using:
Previous place: choose a previously used place from the drop-down list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Select a Time Zone</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/timezone/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/configuration/timezone/index.html</guid>
      <description>Suntimes can be configured to use a given time zone (or other time standards).
System Time Zone User-Defined Time Zone Time Standard System Time Zone Suntimes displays time using the system time zone by default.
User-Defined Time Zone Suntimes can display time using a specific time zone.
Choose user-defined, tap to sort the list, then select a time zone from the drop-down.
Tap -&amp;gt; Recommend Time Zone to suggest a time zone closely matching local mean time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>