<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>App Dialogs on Suntimes</title>
    <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in App Dialogs on Suntimes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:16:14 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Main</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/main/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/main/index.html</guid>
      <description>Location Current Time Next Event Sunrise, Sunset, Twilight Moon Solstice, Equinox Location Suntimes displays the location name and coordinates in the action bar.
Tap to change the location.
Tap to update the current location.
Tap to show the location on a map. Visibility of the map button can be changed from Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings User Interface -&amp;gt; Show Map Button.
Current Time Suntimes displays the current time and time zone in the upper left.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/sun/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/sun/index.html</guid>
      <description>Current Position Light map Altitude Graph Seek Altitude Play (animation) View date Object Shadow Current Position Suntimes displays the sun&amp;rsquo;s current azimuth and altitude, azimuth at sunrise and sunset, and altitude at solar noon.
Light map Suntimes can display a graph of daylight and twilight periods.
Tip Use Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings User Interface -&amp;gt; Show Light Map to show the light map view on the main screen.
Altitude Graph Use : -&amp;gt; Altitude Graph to toggle the altitude graph, and : -&amp;gt; Options to change the graph&amp;rsquo;s options.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/moon/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/moon/index.html</guid>
      <description>Phase, Illumination, and Position Playback Moonrise, moonset Synodic Month Anomalistic Month More Options Phase, Illumination, and Position Suntimes displays the moon&amp;rsquo;s current phase, illumination, azimuth, and altitude.
Tip Use Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings User Interface -&amp;gt; Show Moon to show this info in the main table.
Playback Use : -&amp;gt; Playback to show the controls.
Tap and to step through positions at 5 minute intervals. Tap to reset to the current time (on the selected day).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solstice, Equinox</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/solstice/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/solstice/index.html</guid>
      <description>Solstices, Equinoxes (tracking) Cross-Quarter Days Tropical Year More Options Solstices, Equinoxes (tracking) Suntimes displays the solstices and equinoxes, and can track the number of days until or since those events.
Use : -&amp;gt; Track to change tracking to the recent, nearest, or upcoming event.
This option can also be changed from the User Interface settings. Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings User Interface -&amp;gt; Solstice Tracking.
Tip Tracking can be enabled in the main view using Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings User Interface -&amp;gt; Show Solstice / Equinox.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Map</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/worldmap/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:16:14 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/dialogs/worldmap/index.html</guid>
      <description>Maps Map Options Play Share (Record) View Date Set Background Maps Basic Blue Marble Polar (North) Polar (South) Azimuthal Equidistant (Phoenix) Map Options Use : -&amp;gt; Options to change the map&amp;rsquo;s options.
Sunlight (shadow) Moonlight Location (dot) Graticule (minor grid lines) Major Lines (equator, tropics, arctic circle) Note The map options are also applied to home screen widgets.
Play (animation) Suntimes can animate the world map at different rates.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>