<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">

    <string name="help_battery_optimization"><xliff:g id="appName">%s</xliff:g> must be \"not optimized\" for best results.</string>  <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_battery_optimization_aggressive">This is a <xliff:g id="manufacturer" example="Samsung">%s</xliff:g> device, which may require additional configuration to work correctly.</string>  <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_restricted_bucket">The application has been placed in the rare or restricted app standby bucket. Alarms may fail to work reliably.</string>    <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_datasources">
        <![CDATA[
        Suntimes uses third-party libraries to perform astronomical calculations.<br/>
        <br/>
        The <b>data source</b> setting allows choosing between different libraries (or choosing between different algorithms offered by those libraries). The default is <b>time4a-time4j</b>.<br/>
        <br/>
        This setting affects the speed and accuracy of calculations, and may limit which features are available. <br/>
        <br/>
        For more information about available choices, or extending the app to support other libraries, see the online help.
    ]]>
    </string>   <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_appearance_allowresize"><![CDATA[
      <big>Swap layouts to fill available space</big><br/><br/>
      <i><b>[enabled]</b></i> The widget will switch between layouts depending on available space.<br/><br/>
      <i><b>[disabled]</b></i> The widget maintains its initial layout when resized. Use this with the \"<i>scale text and icons</i>\" option for extra large widgets.<br/>
    ]]></string>  <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_appearance_widgetlayout"><![CDATA[
      This widget was created with a <b>%1$s</b> <em>initial layout</em>.<br/></br/>
    ]]></string>  <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_appearance_title"><![CDATA[
        The following title substitutions are supported:<br/>
        <br/>
        <b>All Widgets:</b> <br />
                * <b>%d</b> for date (e.g. February 12) <br/>
                * <b>%dd</b> for day (short) (e.g. Mon) <br/>
                * <b>%dD</b> for day (long) (e.g. Monday) <br/>
                * <b>%dY</b> for year (e.g. 2018) <br/>
                * <b>%dt</b> for time (of last update) <br/>
                * <b>%dT</b> for time with seconds (of last update) <br/>
                * <b>%dm</b> for milliseconds (of last update) <br/>
                <br/>
                * <b>%loc</b> for label (e.g. Amsterdam) <br />
                * <b>%lat</b> for latitude <br />
                * <b>%lon</b> for longitude <br/>
                * <b>%lel</b> for elevation (e.g. 0 meters) <br/>
                <br/>
                * <b>%s</b> for data source (e.g. sunrisesunsetlib) <br/>
                * <b>%t</b> for time zone (id) (e.g. CET) <br/>
                * <b>%id</b> for appWidgetID <br/>
         <br/>
         <b>Sun Widgets:</b> <br/>
                * <b>%m</b> for mode (short) (e.g. Civil) <br/>
                * <b>%M</b> for mode (long) (e.g. Civil Twilight) <br/>
                * <b>%o</b> for order (e.g. Last/Next, Today) <br/>
         <br/>
         <b>Moon Widgets:</b> <br/>
                * <b>%i</b> for moon illumination (e.g. 25%) <br/>
                * <b>%M</b> for moon phase (e.g. Waxing Crescent) <br/>
                * <b>%o</b> for order (e.g. Last/Next, Today) <br/>
         <br/>
         <b>Solstice Widgets:</b> <br/>
                * <b>%m</b> for mode (short) (e.g. Solstice) <br/>
                * <b>%M</b> for mode (long) (e.g. Winter Solstice) <br/>
                * <b>%o</b> for order (e.g. Closest Event, Upcoming Event) <br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->


    <string name="help_general_calendarFormatPattern"><![CDATA[
          <b>Date Format:</b> A date format pattern.<br/>
          <br/>Available elements may differ between calendars, but usually include..<br/>
          <br/>
          <b>E</b> : day of week <br/>
          <b>d</b> : day of month <br/>
          <b>D</b> : day of year <br/>
          <b>F</b> : weekday in month <br/>
          <b>M</b> : month of year <br/>
          <b>y</b> : year of era <br/>
          <b>G</b> : era <br/>
          <br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_general_moondialog"><![CDATA[
          \n[Icon Rising]  moonrise \t\t[Icon Noon]  lunar noon
          \n[Icon Setting]  moonset \t\t[Icon Midnight]  lunar midnight
          \n\nShare [Icon Share] will copy text to the clipboard.
    ]]></string>   <!-- each [Icon LABEL] is replaced with an actual icon at runtime --> <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_general_timeMode2_1"><![CDATA[
          <b>Winter/Spring Cross-Quarter:</b> The midpoint between Winter Solstice and Spring Equinox; <em>February</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>August</em> [southern hemisphere].<br/><br/>
          <b>Spring/Summer Cross-Quarter:</b> The midpoint between Spring Equinox and Summer Solstice; <em>May</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>November</em> [southern hemisphere].<br/><br/>
          <b>Summer/Autumn Cross-Quarter:</b> The midpoint between Summer Solstice and Autumnal Equinox; <em>August</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>February</em> [southern hemisphere].<br/><br/>
          <b>Autumn/Winter Cross-Quarter:</b> The midpoint between Autumnal Equinox and Winter Solstice; <em>November</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>May</em> [southern hemisphere].<br/>
    ]]></string>   <!-- help contents: cross-quarter days -->   <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_eventlist"><![CDATA[
          [Icon OK] Choose a custom event.\n
          [Icon Add] Add, [Icon Edit] edit, or [Icon Delete] delete custom events.\n
          \nCustom events can be displayed by the app, by home screen widgets, or used to schedule alarms and notifications.\n
          [Icon View] Marked events are displayed by the app.
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_alarms_bedtime"><![CDATA[
           [Icon Bedtime] Bedtime mode can be used to schedule <b>Do Not Disturb</b> during sleep hours.<br/>
           <br/>
           [Icon Reminder] Show a reminder notification before bedtime.<br/>
           [Icon Alarm] Schedule a wake up alarm for the next morning.<br/><br/>
    ]]></string>  <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_alarms_edit"><![CDATA[
          [Icon Back] to cancel without making changes.<br/>
          [Icon Save] to save, and [Icon Done] to save and enable.<br/>
          [Icon Cancel] to save and disable.<br/>
          [Icon Delete] to cancel and delete.<br/>
          <br/>
          [Icon Offset] is shown when the scheduled time is offset before or after the event time.
    ]]></string>   <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_general_dst"><![CDATA[
          <b>Day Light Saving:</b> [Icon DST] is shown when the current time applies <b>DST</b>, or has been adjusted by a similar rule.<br/><br/>
    ]]></string>   <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_general_actualTime"><![CDATA[
          <b>Actual Time:</b> The approximate time of sunrise and sunset.<br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_general_twilight"><![CDATA[
          <b>Civil Twilight:</b> The sun is 6 degrees below the horizon; the brightest stars are visible. There is enough light for most outdoor activities without requiring a light.<br/><br/>
          <b>Nautical Twilight:</b> The sun is 12 degrees below the horizon; object outlines and the horizon are increasingly indistinct. There isn\'t enough light for most outdoor activities without requiring a light.<br/><br/>
          <b>Astronomical Twilight:</b> The sun is 18 degrees below the horizon. Near darkness of night.<br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_general_riseSetOrder"><![CDATA[
          <b>Today:</b> Rising and setting event times for today\'s date.<br/><br/>
          <b>Last / Next:</b> The time of the last event, and the next upcoming event.<br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->

    <string name="help_general_timeMode2"><![CDATA[
          <b>Spring Equinox:</b> The start of astronomical spring; <em>March</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>September</em> [southern hemisphere]. The March equinox is also called the <em>northward equinox</em>.<br/><br/>
          <b>Summer Solstice:</b> The start of astronomical summer; <em>June</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>December</em> [southern hemisphere]. The June solstice is also called the <em>northern solstice</em>.<br/><br/>
          <b>Autumn Equinox:</b> The start of astronomical autumn; <em>September</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>March</em> [southern hemisphere]. The September equinox is also called the <em>southward equinox</em>.<br/><br/>
          <b>Winter Solstice:</b> The start of astronomical winter; <em>December</em> [northern hemisphere], or <em>June</em> [southern hemisphere]. The December solstice is also called the <em>southern solstice</em>.<br/>
    ]]></string>    <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_general_tropicalyear"><![CDATA[
          <b>Tropical Year:</b> A full cycle of the seasons. The length of the <em>tropical year</em> is measured from one <em>March equinox</em> to the next. It is <em>~365.24 days</em> on average, with an exact length that varies each year (up to 30 minutes).<br/>
    ]]></string>   <!-- TODO -->
    <string name="help_general_solartime"><![CDATA[
          <b>Apparent Solar Time:</b> Sundial time. The time determined by tracking the motion of the apparent sun with respect to a given longitude and latitude.
          <br/><br/>
          The motion of the apparent sun is not constant. It varies seasonally due to the obliquity of the ecliptic and eccentricity of the Earth\'s orbit.
          The length of each apparent solar day, measured from one noon to the next, may be slightly longer or shorter than 24 hours (up to 30s).
          These small variations accumulate with each passing day (and average out over the course of the year).
          <br/><br/>

          <b>Local Mean Time:</b> Clock time. The time determined from the position of the mean sun with respect to a given longitude.
          <br/><br/>
          The motion of the mean sun corrects for obliquity and eccentricity and is uniform.
          The length of each mean solar day is exactly 24 hours.<br/><br/>

          <b>Equation of Time (EOT):</b> The difference between local mean time and apparent solar time.
          This is the accumulated variation of the apparent solar day.
          <br/><br/>
          Apparent solar time may differ from local mean time by up to 16 minutes depending on the season.
          <br/><br/>

          <i>This app uses an algorithm to calculate the equation of time (and derive the apparent solar time).
          Your location is used to determine the local mean time.</i>
          <br/><br/>

    ]]></string>
    <string name="help_general_daylength"><![CDATA[
        <b>Length of day:</b> The amount of time between sunrise and sunset.<br/><br/>
        <b>Usable light:</b> The amount of time between morning and evening civil twilight.<br/>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="help_general_moonillum"><![CDATA[
        <b>Moon Illumination:</b> The main page displays the moon\'s illumination at lunar noon, while the moon dialog displays the moon\'s current illumination.<br/>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="help_general_goldhour"><![CDATA[
        <b>Golden Hour:</b> The sun is between 6 degrees above or below the horizon. In the morning the golden hour begins with civil twilight and ends a short time after sunrise. In the evening the golden hour begins a short time before sunset and ends with civil twilight.<br/>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="help_general_bluehour"><![CDATA[
        <b>Blue Hour:</b> The sun is between 8 degrees and 4 degrees below the horizon. The start and end of the blue hour falls between nautical and civil twilight.<br/>
    ]]></string>
    <string name="help_action_launch"><![CDATA[
        See <b>Intents and Intent Filters</b> <small>(https://developer.android.com/guide/components/intents-filters)</small>.
        <br/><br/>
        All fields are optional (values may be left empty for an <em>implicit intent</em>).
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <b>Action:</b> An action string.<br/><small>e.g. <em>android.intent.action.VIEW</em></small>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <b>Class:</b> A fully qualified class name.<br/><small>e.g. <em>suntimeswidget.SuntimesActivity</em></small>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <b>Data:</b> A Uri that contains or points to attached data. Supports <em>%s</em>ubstitutions. <small>e.g. <em>geo:%lat,%lon</em></small>
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <b>Mime:</b> The mime type of attached data.
        <br/>
        <br/>
        <b>Extras:</b> An <em>&amp;</em> delimited string containing extra values. Supports <em>%s</em>ubstitutions.<br/><br/>Values may be <em>int</em>, <em>long</em>, <em>double</em>, <em>float</em>, <em>boolean</em> or String. <small>e.g. <em>key1=value1 & int=1 & long=1L & double=1D & float=1F & bool=true & etc=%dm</em></small>
    ]]></string> <!-- TODO: added Package: -->
    <string name="help_widgetlist"><![CDATA[
          To <b>add</b> or <b>remove</b> a widget you must navigate to the home screen.<br/><br/>
          To <b>reconfigure</b> an existing widget you can select from the following list.<br/>
    ]]></string>
    <!--<string name="help_alarmclock" />-->
    <string name="help_themelist">
          [Icon Add] Add a new theme or [Icon Copy] copy from an existing theme.\n
          \n
          [Icon Edit] Edit or [Icon Delete] delete themes.\n
          The [Icon Default] default themes cannot be modified.\n
    </string>

    <string name="help_calendar"><![CDATA[Supply events to the Calendar app (moon phases, solstices, and equinoxes).<br />
        <br />
        <u><b><font color="#ff9900">Calendar integration was removed in version v0.10.0.</font></b></u><br />
        <br />
        This feature is now available as a <a href="moreInfoLink">separate app</a>.
    ]]></string>

    <string name="help_worldmap_background">
      <xliff:g id="projectionName" example="Azimuthal Equidistant">%1$s</xliff:g> (<xliff:g id="centerLatitude" example="0">%2$s</xliff:g>, <xliff:g id="centerLongitude" example="0">%3$s</xliff:g>)
      \n\n<xliff:g id="proj4String" example="+proj4=eqd ..">%4$s</xliff:g>
      \n\nFor best results select an image matching these properties.
    </string>    <!-- TODO -->

</resources>