<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alarms on Suntimes</title>
    <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alarms on Suntimes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:50:03 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Set Alarm</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/setalarm/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/setalarm/index.html</guid>
      <description>Alarm Types Schedule by Time Schedule by Event Show Alarm Time Alarm Types Suntimes supports multiple alarm types. Tap to choose the type.
Alarms will sound until they are dismissed or snoozed. Notifications remain in the tray until they are dismissed. Quick Notifications are shown for a brief moment. Tip Quick Notifications are automatically dismissed after 30s (changed from Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; Alarms -&amp;gt; Auto-dismiss after). Regular notifications will remain the tray until they are dismissed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edit Alarm</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/editalarm/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/editalarm/index.html</guid>
      <description>Type Label Note Event (or time) Repeat Offset (before/after) Location Reminder Sound Vibration On Alert Action On Dismiss Action On Dismiss Challenge Tap to cancel without making changes.
Tap to save, or to save and enable.
Tap to save and disable.
Tap to cancel and delete.
Type Tap to change the alarm type:
Alarm Notification Quick Notification Tip Quick Notifications are automatically dismissed after 30s. Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; Alarms -&amp;gt; Auto-dismiss after to change this setting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm List</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/alarmlist/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/alarmlist/index.html</guid>
      <description>Alarm List Select, Deselect Add Alarm Edit Alarm Delete, Clear Snooze, Dismiss Sort Alarms Export, Import Alarm List The alarm list can be shown from Suntimes -&amp;gt; Set Alarm, or by tapping Suntimes Alarms from the app launcher.
Tip Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; Alarms -&amp;gt; Launcher Icon to enable the Suntimes Alarms icon in the app launcher.
Select, Deselect Tap an item in the list to select it. Selected items display the alarm note and additional controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Settings</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/settings/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/settings/index.html</guid>
      <description>Suntimes -&amp;gt; Settings -&amp;gt; Alarms to reach alarm settings.
Alarms Dismiss Challenge None (default) Easy Math. Solve single digit math problems to dismiss alarms. Reminder within Show a reminder notification within 12 hours of each alarm.
Snooze for Snooze alarms for up to 120 minutes.
Snooze limit Change the snooze limit to limit the number of times snooze can be used.
Timeout after Alarms will timeout after sounding for too long without user intervention.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alarm Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/recommendations/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:50:03 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://forrestguice.codeberg.page/Suntimes/help/alarms/recommendations/index.html</guid>
      <description>Battery Optimization Notification Settings Autostart Permission Battery Optimization Suntimes must be not optimized for alarms to work reliably.
Settings -&amp;gt; Apps -&amp;gt; Suntimes -&amp;gt; Battery -&amp;gt; Unrestricted
Note On most devices the optimized setting may delay alarms up to 15 minutes. Other devices may restrict alarms without special configuration.
The following devices are affected: Asus, Blackview, Huawei, LENOVO, Meizu, OnePlus, OPPO, realme, Samsung, Sony, Unihertz, Vivo, WIKO, and Xiaomi. Check https://dontkillmyapp.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>